gifttree.com 2008-12-18

# GiftTree Privacy Policy & Security Statement

## Privacy Policy Statement

This is the web site of **GiftTree.com**  

Our postal address is   
**1800 W. Fourth Plain Blvd, Ste 120-B  
Vancouver, WA 98660**

We can be reached via [e-mail](http://www.gifttree.com/helppgs/mail.php "GiftTree Email") or you can reach us by telephone at **1 (800) 379-4065**

For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes the consumer's domain name and e-mail address (where possible).

We collect the domain name and e-mail address (where possible) of visitors to our Web page, the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, the e-mail addresses of those who make postings to our chat areas, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, user-specific information on what pages consumers access or visit, information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations, no information on consumers who browse our Web page and the information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web page, used to customize the content and/or layout of our page for each individual visitor, used to notify consumers about updates to our Web site, used by us to contact consumers for marketing purposes, not shared with other organizations for commercial purposes.

With respect to cookies: We use cookies to store visitors preferences, record session information, such as items that consumers add to their shopping cart, record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit, alert visitors to new areas that we think might be of interest to them when they return to our site, record past activity at a site in order to provide better service when visitors return to our site, customize Web page content based on visitors' browser type or other information that the visitor sends.

If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by sending us e-mail at the above address, writing to us at the above address, visiting us at <http://www.gifttree.com/common/nnews.php>.

From time to time, we make our _customer_ e-mail list available to other reputable organizations whose products or services we think you might find interesting. If you do not want us to share your e-mail address with other companies or organizations, please let us know by sending us e-mail at the above address, writing to us at the above address.

If you supply us with your postal address on-line you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please let us know by sending us e-mail at the above address, writing to us at the above address.

You may receive mailings from other reputable companies. You can, however, have your name put on our do-not-share list by sending us e-mail at the above address, writing to us at the above address. Please provide us with your exact name and address. We will be sure your name is removed from the list we share with other organizations.

Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers on-line may receive telephone contact from us with information regarding new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such telephone calls, please let us know by sending us e-mail at the above address, writing to us at the above address. Please provide us with your name and phone number. We will be sure your name is removed from the list we share with other organizations. 

With respect to Ad Servers: We do not partner with or have special relationships with any ad server companies.

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will use for these new purposes only data collected from the time of the policy change forward. Customers may prevent their information from being used for purposes other than those for which it was originally collected by sending us e-mail at the above address, writing to us at the above address

Upon request we provide site visitors with access to all information that we maintain about them, financial information (e.g., credit card account information) that we maintain about them, unique identifier information (e.g., customer number or password) that we maintain about them, transaction information (e.g., dates on which customers made purchases, amounts and types of purchases) that we maintain about them, communications that the consumer/visitor has directed to our site (e.g., e-mails, customer inquiries), contact information (e.g., name, address, phone number) that we maintain about them , a description of information that we maintain about them. Consumers can access this information by e-mail us at the above address, calling us at the above phone number, writing to us at the above address, visiting us at My Account (most personal information can be accessed and changed from here).

Upon request we offer visitors the ability to have inaccuracies corrected in contact information, financial information, unique identifiers, transaction information, communications that the consumer/visitor has directed to the site. Consumers can have this information corrected by sending us e-mail at the above address, calling us at the above telephone number, writing to us at the above address, visiting us at My Account (most personal information can be accessed and changed from here).

With respect to security: When we transfer and receive certain types of sensitive information such as financial information, we redirect visitors to a secure server, you will know that you are in a secure part of the site by looking for the lock symbol in the lower right corner of your computer screen or by looking at the url address (it will begin with https instead of http). We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site.

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above addresses or phone number.

Please see our Terms of Use for further information.

© 2008 GiftTree All Rights Reserved.
